http://www.duisantacruz.com/privacy-policy

Underage (Under 21) DUI
License Suspension Hearings (DMV)
Underage (Under 21) DUI
License Suspension Hearings (DMV)
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy applies to information collected online from users of this website. In this policy, you can learn what kind of information we collect, when and how we might use that information, how we protect the information, and the choices you have with respect to your personal information.
What personal information is collected through this website and how is it used?
We collect information about our users in three ways: directly from the user, from our Web server logs and through cookies. We use the information primarily to provide you with a personalized Internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you. We don't share any of the information you provide with others, unless we say so in this Privacy Policy, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.
User-supplied information: If you fill out the "contact" form on this website, we will ask you to provide some personal information (such as e-mail address, name, phone number and state). We only require that you provide an e-mail address, and that information, along with any additional information you voluntarily provide, will be used so that we may respond to your inquiry. We may use information to communicate with you in the future. If you do not wish to receive such communications, you may opt out (unsubscribe) as described below.
Web server logs: When you visit our website, we may track information about your visit and store that information in web server logs, which are records of the activities on our sites. The servers automatically capture and save the information electronically. Examples of the information we may collect include:
your unique Internet protocol address;
the name of your unique Internet service provider;
the town/city, county/state and country from which you access our website;
the kind of browser or computer you use;
he number of links you click within the site;
the date and time of your visit;
the web page from which you arrived to our site;
the pages you viewed on the site; and
certain searches/queries that you conducted via our website(s).
The information we collect in web server logs helps us administer the site, analyze its usage, protect the website and its content from inappropriate use and improve the user's experience.
Cookies: In order to offer and provide a customized and personal service, our websites and applications may use cookies to store and help track information about you. Cookies are simply small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to help remind us who you are and to help you navigate our sites during your visits. Cookies allow us to save passwords and preferences for you so you won't have to re-enter them each time you visit.
The use of cookies is relatively standard. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. However, if you prefer, you can set your browser to either notify you when you receive a cookie, or to refuse to accept cookies. You should understand that some features of many sites may not function properly if you don't accept cookies.
How is personal information protected?
We take certain appropriate security measures to help protect your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized persons will always be unable to defeat our security measures.
Who has access to the information?
We will not sell, rent, or lease mailing lists or other user data to others, and we will not make your personal information available to any unaffiliated parties, except as follows:
to agents and/or contractors who may use it on our behalf or in connection with their relationship with us; and
as required by law, in a matter of public safety or policy, as needed in connection with the transfer of our business assets (for example, if we are acquired by another firm or if we are liquidated during bankruptcy proceedings), or if we believe in good faith that sharing the data is necessary to protect our rights or property.
How can I correct, amend or delete my personal information and/or opt out of future communications?
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. Contact us via the phone number or contact form on our website at any time to:
see what data we have about you, if any;
change/correct any data we have about you;
ask us to delete any data we have about you; and/or
opt out of future communications from us.
If you have any additional questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us via the phone number listed on this website.
Practice Areas
Criminal DefenseDriving Under the Influence
Recent Blog Posts
All DMV Offices Will Open for Business Thursday, June 11 With Precautions TakenWhat if I Can’t Afford a Private Attorney When Charged With a Crime in Santa Cruz?How Can a DUI Arrest Affect My Reputation?DUI Chemical Test Refusal – Almost Always a Bad IdeaWhat Are My Rights if I Am Arrested By a Police Officer?
Home
Firm Overview
Attorney Profile
Practice Areas
Articles
Blog
Contact
The Santa Cruz, California office of John W. Thornton, Attorney at Law provides skilled and knowledgeable criminal defense representation to residents of Santa Cruz County, including Santa Cruz, Aptos, Ben Lomond, Big Basin, Boulder Creek, Brookdale, Capitola, Corralitos, Davenport, Felton, Freedom, La Selva Beach, Las Lomas, Lompico, Los Gatos, Mount Hermon, Pajaro, Paradise Park, Rio del Mar, Royal Oaks, Scotts Valley, Seacliff, Seascape, Soquel and Watsonville.
Resources |
Privacy Policy
Disclaimer |
Sitemap
© 2020 John W. Thornton, Attorney at Law
303 Potrero Street, Suite 30, Santa Cruz, CA 95060 | 831-426-5800
